15 Kingfisher Greenside Mutare, Zimbabwe +263 774 797 837 tmupasiri123@gmail.com

# Tinotenda Mupasiri

Hiring Manager HR Department

#### **Dear HR Manager**

I am writing this letter to express my abundant interest in working for you at your company. I am an IT expert specializing in various fields such as web development, network troubleshooting, system administration, software development and hardware repair. These skills apply to both PC and Mobile devices.

I have experience in different fields at different places that verify each of the above-mentioned skills. Am a young man ready to start and learn at any position you deem appropriate. Am looking forward to hearing from you in regards to an interview or otherwise.

Sincerely,

Tinotenda Mupasiri

# — TINOTENDA RICHARD MUPASIRI —

IT SPECIALIST / DIGITAL MARKETER

#### CONTACT

- +263 774797837
- LinkedIn
- tmupasiri123@gmail.com
  - TM portfolio website
  - Projects on GitHub

#### **SKILLS**

- FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT
- DIGITAL MARKETING
- UI/UX DESIGN
- COMPUTER REPAIR
- NETWORK TROUBLESHOOTING
- PRESENTATIONS

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Mutare Polytechnic**

From May 2015 – To March 2020

Completed National Certificate and National Diploma in Information Technology. Majoring subjects included Programming in C++, Computer Architecture and servicing, Software Design, Data Communications and Networks, Database Architecture and Concepts, Internet and Web Design, Data Structures and Algorithms using C++.

#### **Front End Libraries**

Issued August 2021 (No Expiration date)

Completed Front end libraries course on <a href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/t\_mavrick">https://www.freecodecamp.org/t\_mavrick</a>. The course covers programming languages including Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, React and Redux as well as 5 completed and verified Projects.

#### **Backend Libraries**

Issued February 2022 (No Expiration date)
Completed Data Visualization course on <a href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/t\_mavrick">https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/t\_mavrick</a>. The course covers web hosting, version control, cloud computing, database management, information security and API network configuration.

#### **PROFILE**

Greetings. I am Tinotenda or Richard, whichever name is comfortable for your tongue. I am born and raised in Mutare, Zimbabwe. I am an IT Specialist as well as an as piring junior full stack web developer although my strengths lie in the front-end development. I work very hard and I am dedicated to completing tasks on time, also work fairly well with others. My supporting documents are also within this document. Looking forward to new experiences and learning as much as I can!!

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### InfoHoldings | IT Technician

January 2018–August 2018

As an intern my responsibilities included answering company phone calls, Wi-Fi network administration, Printer administration and servicing, Computer servicing and troubleshooting, Software installation and updates, Preparing projector and computer devices for meeting. As InfoHoldings is a data analytics company I was also tasked with Data entry, formatting, organization, verification and validation of data, data storage and backup.

# Manica Boards and Doors | IT Technician and Specialist

September 2018–December 2018

As an intern my responsibilities included Answering company and IT office calls, remote IT support, Printer administration and servicing, Network administration and troubleshooting, Network cable making and management, Systems administration and error troubleshooting, Software installation and updates, Computer servicing and troubleshooting and hardware installation.

## Puma Energy | Freelance Web Developer

May 2021-November 2021

As a junior developer I was responsible for creating a basic login or signup page and the landing page after logging in. The website was constructed using React and JavaScript and Firebase for Authentication, Database and Hosting.